

# **JULIO CACERES**

Front-End Web Developer

### **DEVELOPMENT SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS (Vanilla, Tailwind, bootstrap, Material UI, Flowbite, Vuetify, Element)
- JavaScript (React, Redux, React-Router, Vue)
- PHP (Laravel)
- **NODEJS (Express)**
- Databases (Postgres, Mysql, MsSql Server)
- Tools (Git, Github, WebPack, Vite, Jira)
- Testing Libraries (Jest, Chai, Mocha, PHP unit, Vitest)

# **ITC SKILLS**

- CI /CD
- Networking
- Virtualization and Containers.
- Sys. Admin (Windows server, Linux base systems)
- Cloud (AWS, G-cloud)



#### Contact:



Jccaceres01@gmail.com



+1 809-852-1175



👤 Leonardo Vidal #34 Maimón. RD.



https://jccaceres01.github.io

## **PROFILE**



Hello! I'm a passionate front-end developer with experience creating engaging and interactive user interfaces using the React JavaScript library. My goal is to combine my passion for programming with my love for design to create exceptional digital experiences.

## **EDUCATION**



Bachelor Degree in information technology, UASD, (No finished).

2008 - 2013

High School, Colegio mi Pequeño Hogar

2003 - 2006

School, Colegio mi Pequeño Hogar.

1996 - 2002

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**



Web Developer, SOCOCO de Costa Rica.

2015 - 2022

IT Manager Assistant, CORMIDOM.

2009 - 2015